Office of Undergraduate Education Records UA049
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Dean of Undergraduate Education records, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005724; 9.1 Megabytes; 20 Digital Object(s) 20 digital objects comprising 178 files.
  - Jim Glaser records, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005725; 9.1 Megabytes; 20 Digital Object(s) 20 digital objects comprising 178 files.
    - Reorganization, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005740; 527.6 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 3 files.
      Dean of Undergraduate Education job description; description of Undergraduate Education Committees; and Arts, Sciences, & Engeineering reorganization presentation.
    - Reports, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005741; 1.7 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 14 files.
      Reports and data regarding early graduation, honors theses, the Resumed Education for Adult Learning (REAL) program, scholarships, and the student experience and New England Association of Schools and Colleges (NEASC) reports.
    - Retention Task Force, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005742; 1.7 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 40 files.
      Undergraduate Retention Task Force notes, reports, and related documents.
    - Summer scholars, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005743; 113.7 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.
      Summer Scholars Program Evaluation and list of scholars.
    - Year-end reports, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005744; 407.5 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
      Dean of Undergraduate Education year-end reports.
    - Yearly communications, circa 2003 -- 2010; UA049.005745; 343 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 7 files.
      Communications sent to Tufts students' parents.
- Additional accessions, UA049.005718
  - College of Arts and Sciences Undergraduate Research and Scholarship Symposium, March 2000, 2000-03; UA049-001 (Box 1)
  - Fall Orientation Calendar, 2007; UA049-002 (Box 2)
  - Photographs of Balfour Scholars at outdoor retreat, 1990 -- 2000; UA049-019 (Box 2)
  - Jim Glaser subject files, 2003 -- 2010; UA049-003 (Box 3)
  - Writing Across the Curriculum (WAC) records, 1985 -- 2009; UA049-018 (Box 4)